And I'd like to leave you with this thought. On the left is water coming through the shore, taken from a NASA satellite. On the right, there is a coral. Now if you take the mammary gland and spread it and take the fat away, on a dish it looks like that. Do they look the same? Do they have the same patterns? Why is it that nature keeps doing that over and over again? And I'd like to submit to you that we have sequenced the human genome, we know everything about the sequence of the gene, the language of the gene, the alphabet of the gene, But we know nothing, but nothing, about the language and alphabet of form. So, it's a wonderful new horizon, it's a wonderful thing to discover for the young and the passionate old, and that's me. So go to it! (Applause)
Je voudrais vous laisser sur cette pensée. Sur la gauche il y a l'eau qui arrive à la rive, prise depuis un satellite de la NASA. Sur la droite, il y a un corail. Si vous prenez de la glande mammaire et l'étalez et enlevez le gras, elle ressemble à ça sur un plat. Ont-ils le même aspect ? Ont-ils les mêmes modèles ? Pourquoi est-ce que la nature reproduit ce modèle encore et encore ? J'aimerais vous suggérer que nous avons séquencé le génome humain, nous savons tout sur la séquence du gène, la langue du gène, l'alphabet du gène, Mais nous ne savons rien, mais rien, sur la langue et l'alphabet de la forme. C'est donc un nouvel horizon merveilleux, C'est une chose merveilleuse à découvrir pour les jeunes et les vieux passionnés, dont je fais partie. Alors allez-y ! (Applaudissements)